const e="english",o=200,a=75,t=[{id:76,question:"I shall find time for my ……… when I get …… with this difficult assignment.",option:{a:"Pat time /over",b:"pass-time/over",c:"pastime/through",d:"pastime/through"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:77,question:"Agbo says he is not afraid of ………",option:{a:"anybody",b:"nothing",c:"nobody",d:"no one"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:78,question:"It is …….. responsibility to look after their parents in old age.",option:{a:"theirs’",b:"their",c:"theirs",d:"their’s"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:79,question:"One needs to exemplify or ………. the aspect of the subject being discussed",option:{a:"supply",b:"declare",c:"satisfy",d:"demonstrate"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:80,question:"……………his illness, Muhammad could not come to school.",option:{a:"with reference to",b:"referring to",c:"owing to",d:"due to ."},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:81,question:"After so many trials, the experiment………….",option:{a:"paid up",b:"paid for",c:"paid out",d:"paid off"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:82,question:"People dislike Mariam because she is ……………",option:{a:"trickful",b:" trickish",c:"trickly",d:"tricker"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:83,question:"The reporter said that the Honourable speaker………….. impeached ",option:{a:"is to be",b:"might have been",c:"may have being",d:"will have been"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:84,question:"Actually, he forgot the one to …………… the job was given.",option:{a:"whom",b:"who",c:"whomever",d:"whoever"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:85,question:"You may not have heard the last word on the matter……..",option:{a:"may you have",b:"haven’t you",c:"have you",d:"mayn’t have you?"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:86,question:"All God’s prophets were given the great……….to preach salvation to people.",option:{a:"commission",b:"commition",c:"commission",d:"commission"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:87,question:"Ali goes to the stadium regularly, but he …………… to the church for months.",option:{a:"hasn’t been",b:"haven’t been",c:"didn’t go",d:"hadn’t been"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:88,question:"Each of the houses…………",option:{a:" have got",b:" Have",c:"has",d:"were given a new look."},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:89,question:"The minister addressed the workers to boost their…………",option:{a:" Morale",b:"morality",c:" mural",d:" moral"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:90,question:"I don’t coming home, is he?......... he is isn’t.",option:{a:"Yes",b:"No",c:"won",d:"now"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:91,question:"………..as a federal capital only……….. the last twenty years.",option:{a:"has existed/for",b:"existed/over",c:"was existing/from",d:"is existing/in"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:92,question:"No teacher of honour would subject his student to any form of ……..",option:{a:"harassment",b:"Harassment",c:"harassment",d:"harassment"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:93,question:"Each producer  is able to place a price on his product by considering its…………",option:{a:"worth",b:"choice",c:"judgement",d:"assessment"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:94,question:"The police claim that a number of stolen cars…………. recovered.",option:{a:"has being",b:"is being",c:"has been",d:"have been"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:95,question:"The storm………….. Havoc on several buildings in the village.",option:{a:"wreaked",b:"wrecked",c:"made",d:"did"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:96,question:"The chairman refused to shake…………. with the secretary",option:{a:"hand",b:"his hand",c:"hands",d:"his hands"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:97,question:"The poor widow who could not buy the clothes was seen…….her wool into……….yesterday",option:{a:"to spin/yards",b:"spinning/yarn",c:"making/tailoring",d:"to spill/clothes"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:98,question:"He not only looked after the children when their parents died, ………..sponsored their education to university.",option:{a:"but also",b:"also he",c:"but he",d:"also"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:99,question:"His supporters railed round him in moments of …………..",option:{a:"criticism",b:"Crisis",c:"acrimony",d:"disillusionment."},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:100,question:"The interpreter was wrong because he gave the congregation a ………… translation of the pastor’s statement.",option:{a:"literal",b:"unilateral",c:"literary",d:"lateral"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:101,question:"Ju<u>dge</u>",option:{a:"gear",b:"spinach",c:"pleasure",d:"camouflage"},section:"choose the option that has the same consonant sound as the one represented by the letter(s) underline.",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:102,question:"caus<u>ed</u>",option:{a:"chanced",b:"frost",c:"released",d:"realized"},section:"choose the option that has the same consonant sound as the one represented by the letter(s) underline.",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:103,question:"mis<u>chi</u>ef ",option:{a:"Christmas",b:"ritual",c:"Brochure",d:"Champagne"},section:"choose the option that has the same consonant sound as the one represented by the letter(s) underline.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:104,question:"Everyone was ready to play the evil’s advocate in the impeachment controversy.",option:{a:"everyone was willing to speak against the impeachment to encourage discussion on it.",b:"everyone was willing to defend an unpopular point of view concerning the impeachment.",c:"everyone was willing to fight for the defenceless citizens no matter the consequences.",d:"everyone was willing to be an evil genius in the controversy"},section:"that best explains the information conveyed in the sentence.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:105,question:"Adamu’s father is a key figure in that ministry",option:{a:"The ministry trusts Adamu’s father as a central figure",b:"Adamu’s father is a figurehead in the ministry",c:"Adamu’s father’s position is essential in the ministry.",d:"Adamu’s father keeps the key to the ministry."},section:"that best explains the information conveyed in the sentence.",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:106,question:"The government warns that drink-driving is punishable under the law.",option:{a:"a drunkard driving can be punished",b:"driving while drunk is an offence",c:"driving while drinking is an offence",d:"drinking and driving is an offence."},section:"that best explains the information conveyed in the sentence.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:107,question:"In many countries, democracy is ostensibly being practiced.",option:{a:"democracy is indeed being practiced  in many countries",b:"many countries have effective democracy.",c:"many countries have democracy in practice",d:"democracy is apparently practice in many countries."},section:"that best explains the information conveyed in the sentence.",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:108,question:"The investigators stated clearly that they had reached a dead end in their scrutiny of suspects in the murder case.",option:{a:"the investigators did not know what to do with the suspect’s murder",b:"The investigators had evidence to sentence the suspects to death in the end.",c:"there was no further progress in the investigation of the murder suspects.",d:"the end had come for the suspects in the murder case."},section:"that best explains the information conveyed in the sentence.",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:109,question:"",option:{a:" Secondment",b:"Orthopaedic",c:" oriental",d:"photographic"},section:"choose the option that has a different stress pattern from the others.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:110,question:"",option:{a:"ratify",b:" famous",c:" result",d:" taxi"},section:"choose the option that has a different stress pattern from the others.",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:111,question:"Sailors are unusually <i>dauntless</i> in their exploits",option:{a:"selfless",b:"ruthless",c:"excited",d:"frightened"},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:112,question:"The <i>potency</i> of the drug has been acknowledged.",option:{a:"action",b:"loss",c:"inefficacy",d:"power"},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:113,question:"The dictator wanted <i>tractable</i> men in his cabinet.",option:{a:"reliable",b:"intelligent ",c:"tough",d:"unruly"},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:114,question:"After the war, the victors became increasingly <i>vindictive</i>",option:{a:"friendly",b:"vociferous",c:"arrogant",d:"treacherous"},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:115,question:"The ship was <i>imperiled</i> by high winds",option:{a:"piloted",b:"destroyed",c:"deceived",d:"saved"},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:116,question:"Beauty queens sometime wear <i>outlandish</i>  dresses.",option:{a:"beautiful",b:"flashy",c:"familiar",d:"attractive"},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:117,question:"The journalist said he was working <i>freelance</i>",option:{a:"tirelessly",b:"satisfactorily",c:"without a pay",d:"dependently"},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:118,question:"My father’s presentation was rather <i>causal</i>",option:{a:"formal",b:"vital",c:"informal ",d:"divisive"},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:119,question:"The flying Eagles put up a <i>plucky</i> defence against their opponents.",option:{a:"strong",b:"weak",c:"careless",d:"tactful"},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:120,question:"The man who scare the girl was a bit <i>deranged</i>",option:{a:"sane ",b:"amorous",c:"crazy",d:"dangerous"},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:121,question:"The injured man is determined to <i>get back</i> at his assailant.",option:{a:"attack",b:"identify",c:"visit",d:"forgive"},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:122,question:"The player <i>writhed in pain</i> after the fall.",option:{a:"remained still",b:"cried out",c:"walked out",d:"shook violently"},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:123,question:"The noise of the fan <i>unnerved</i>  the star player.",option:{a:"refreshed",b:"confused",c:"helped",d:"calmed"},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:124,question:"The team got <i>an ecstatic</i> welcome from the crowd.",option:{a:"An unexpected",b:"a joyous",c:"a cold",d:"a thunderous"},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:125,question:"We found a <i>shady</i> place for the display.",option:{a:"an open",b:"an unsafe",c:"a stuffy",d:"an enclosed"},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:126,question:"expostulate",option:{a:"exposTUlate",b:"expostuLATE",c:"EXpostulate",d:"exPOStulate"},section:"choose the appropriate stress pattern from the options. The syllables are written in capital letters.",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:127,question:"sufficiency",option:{a:"sufFIciency",b:"SUFficiency",c:"sufficienCY",d:"suffiCIENcy"},section:"choose the appropriate stress pattern from the options. The syllables are written in capital letters.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:128,question:"The town was in such a <i>turmoil</i> that the dance was called off.",option:{a:"mourning state",b:"rainy state",c:"state of darkness",d:"state of confusion"},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:129,question:"The festivals create in the people a feeling of price in the cultural <i>heritage</i>  ",option:{a:"history",b:"heirloom",c:"legacy",d:"possession"},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:130,question:"<i>Funnily enough,</i> the priest prayed for the robber who shot him.",option:{a:"Timidly",b:"Unexpectedly",c:"Disappointingly",d:"Fearlessly."},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:131,question:"The presence of the captain makes the sailors <i>ill at ease</i>.",option:{a:"uncomfortable ",b:"sickly ",c:"impatient",d:"easily ill"},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:132,question:"The press describe the efforts of the government in <i>pejorative</i> terms.",option:{a:"critical",b:"contemptible",c:"palpable",d:"superlative"},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:133,question:"Okonkwo manages his household <i>with a heavy hand.</i>",option:{a:"like a powerful dictator",b:"using the cane on every occasion",c:"without tolerating weakness",d:"like a heavy weight champion."},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:134,question:"The school’s badge is the <i>insignia</i> of office for all the prefects in the school.",option:{a:"Power",b:"symbol",c:"seal",d:"recognition"},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:135,question:"Ibro shows enough <i>liberality</i>  with his meager income.",option:{a:"generosity",b:"frugality",c:"prodigality",d:"insensitivity"},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:136,question:"It is a <i>misnomer</i> to call three thousand naira a living wage.",option:{a:"an incontrovertible assertion",b:"an appropriate term",c:"a wrong description",d:"a mishmash"},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:137,question:"His plans <i>boomeranged</i> on him",option:{a:"bounce",b:"fell",c:"catapulted",d:"backfired"},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:138,question:"The manager’s knowledge of the strike is of <i>the utmost</i>  importance.",option:{a:"standard",b:"genuine",c:"paramount",d:"basic"},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:139,question:"There has been a <i>downturn</i> in the affairs of the company.",option:{a:"a massive increase",b:"little progress",c:"a turn-around",d:"a decline"},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:140,question:"The <i>mottled</i> skin of a person with HIV indicates an advance stage  of its development.",option:{a:"Brown ",b:"spotted",c:"scaly",d:"pimply"},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:141,question:"In spite of constant financial support from his father, Udenyi treats his studies with considerable <i>levity</i>.",option:{a:"seriousness",b:"enthusiasm ",c:"wastefulness",d:"lassitude"},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:142,question:"The prosecutor was fully able to <i>substantiate</i> the charge.",option:{a:"expatiate on",b:"prove",c:"dismiss",d:"weaken"},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:143,question:"The teacher wants MY pen.",option:{a:"Does the teacher want his pen?",b:"What does the teacher want?",c:"Does the teacher want your ruler?",d:"Who wants my pen?"},section:"the word in capital letters has the emphatic stress.  Choose the option to which the given sentence relates.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:144,question:"The student BOUGHT the book.",option:{a:"Who bought the book?",b:"Did the student steal the book?",c:"What did the student buy?",d:"How will the student get the book?"},section:"the word in capital letters has the emphatic stress.  Choose the option to which the given sentence relates.",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:145,question:"n<u>i</u>ne",option:{a:"pint",b:"gill",c:"pin",d:"click"},section:"choose the option that has the same vowel sound as the one represented by the letter(s) underlined.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:146,question:"b<u>ea</u>r",option:{a:"beer",b:"steer",c:"rare",d:"fear"},section:"choose the option that has the same vowel sound as the one represented by the letter(s) underlined.",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:147,question:"",option:{a:" Circulation",b:"eleven",c:" impossible",d:"criticism"},section:"choose the option that has the stress on the first syllable.",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:148,question:"",option:{a:"bachelor",b:"condemn",c:" afternoon",d:"intact "},section:"choose the option that has the stress on the first syllable.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:149,question:"",option:{a:" foul",b:"tout",c:"owl",d:"foe"},section:"choose the option that has a different vowel sound from the others.",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:150,question:"",option:{a:"alter",b:" water",c:" pot",d:"hall"},section:"choose the option that has a different vowel sound from the others.",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2004",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"}],s={subject:e,status:200,total:75,data:t};export{t as data,s as default,o as status,e as subject,a as total};
